Guide to the Michael Francis Blake Photographs, 1912-1934
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Michael Francis Blake photographs 1912-1934
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Blake, Michael Francis
0.6 linear feet Extent: 117 Items
Michael Francis Blake was one of Charleston, S.C.'s first African-American studio photographers. The Michael Francis Blake Photographs Collection consists of 117 photographs of men, women, and children that were taken between 1912-1934.
RL.00133
Language: Material in English
Administrative Information
Online Items
Images from the collection have been digitized and are available in the Michael Francis Blake Photographs, 1912-1934 - Duke Digital Collections
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. There may be a 48-hour delay in obtaining these materials.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Michael Francis Blake Photographs were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 1986.
Biographical Note
Blake, a graduate of Avery Normal Institute, was one of Charleston, S.C.'s first African-American studio photographers. He was born on Johns Island, S.C. and married Cecelia Ford from Georgetown, S.C. in 1899. Blake moved to Charleston, S.C. with his family around 1900 and began to work professionally as a photographer in 1912.
Blake had a studio at 12 W. Sumter Street which later became 384 W. Sumter Street after the street was renumbered in 1918. He also regularly set up his camera on the northwest corner of Radcliffe and King Streets in Charleston.
Collection Overview
The collection consists of the contents of a photographic album entitled "Portraits of Members," containing 117 photographs of men, women, and children, both singly and in groups. The majority of the subjects appear to be African-American. The photographs represent the work of Michael Francis Blake from the 1910s to his death in 1934. However, not all of the photographs have been positively identified as having been taken by Blake. Some of the photographs are stamped with Blake's name and studio addresses. Photograph 28 was taken outside of Blake's studio at #384 West Sumter Street.
The predominant style of the photographs is the formal studio pose, though some formal shots in the collection were taken in other locations. There are some informal snapshots that may or may not have been taken by Blake. Ninety-one of the photos are photographic postcards and the others are either mounted photographs or snapshots. Some photographs were taken outdoors in front of a backdrop and with props such as rugs, chairs and plants to recreate a "studio" portrait.
Some of the photos have what appear to be shopping lists and other notations written on the back of them.
In thirty-five of the photographs subjects have been identified, including one photograph of Michael Francis Blake. The Charleston Museum holds the original negatives of the prints. The collection includes original prints, copy prints made from original negatives and eight negatives. Each has been assigned a unique identifier.
Subject Headings
Blake, Michael Francis, d. 1934; Photography -- United States; Photographs; African Americans -- Portraits; African Americans -- Photographs; African Americans -- South Carolina -- Charleston; African Americans -- South Carolina -- Charleston; African American photographers -- South Carolina -- Charleston; African American photographers -- South Carolina -- Charleston; Charleston (S.C.)--Social life and customs; Photograph albums; African Americans -- South Carolina -- Charleston; African Americans -- South Carolina -- Charleston; African American photographers -- South Carolina -- Charleston; African American photographers -- South Carolina -- Charleston
Contents of Collection
- Michael Francis Blake Photographs, 1912-1934, (1 box)
  - Studio photograph, seated male adult, identified as Michael Francis Blake, circa 1918-1922, MFB001; 3.5 x 5.5 (Box 1)
  - Snapshot, female adult standing by an automobile, unidentified, undated, MFB002; 3.25 x 5.5 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, standing female adult holding a book, unidentified, circa 1926-1939. Identified as by Blake., MFB003; 3.5 x 5.5; Embossed with Blake's studio address. (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, female adult, identified as Lillie Ford, 4 August 1926, MFB004; 3.5 x 5.5; Writing on Photograph: "Lillie Ford taken Aug 4 1926" (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, standing male child, unidentified, circa 1918-1922, MFB005; 3.5 x 5.5 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, standing female adult holding a basket of flowers, identified as Francis Smalls, circa 1918-1922, MFB006; 3.5 x 5.5; Writing on Photograph: "Frances Smalls my niece Frances Georgetown S.C." (Box 1)
  - Snapshot, male child, unidentified, undated, MFB007; 3 x 4.5; Writing on Photograph: "To my dear Aunt Rosa your Nephew Edwin." Stamped "469". (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, standing young male adult, unidentified, undated, MFB008; 3.5 x 5.5 (Box 1)
  - Snapshot, male adult standing by a porch, unidentified, undated, MFB009; 2.75 x 4.25; Writing on Photograph: "Frederick" (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, standing male adult and female adult, unidentified, circa 1910-1918, MFB010; 3.5 x 5.5 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, seated male adult, identified as Jesse E. Beard, a pastor of Morris Brown AME Church and vice president of the People's Federal Bank in Charleston, S.C., undated, MFB011; 3.5 x 5.5; Embossed with Blake's studio address. (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, standing child, unidentified, circa 1918-1922, MFB012; 3.5 x 5.5 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, seated infant propped up on a chair, unidentified, 1933 June 29, MFB013; 3.5 x 5.5; Writing on Photograph: "Taken Thursday 29/33 - June Age 3 months." Embossed with Blake's studio address. (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, male adult, unidentified, circa 1910-1918, MFB014; 3.5 x 5.5; Stamped with Blake's studio address: "M.F. Blake View Photographer 12 W. Sumter Street. Phone 1341-L, Charleston, S.C." (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, seated female adult, unidentified, circa 1910-1918, MFB015; 3.5 x 5.5 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, child standing on a chair and an infant seated on a chair, identified as Bennie children, circa 1926-1939. Photograph identified as by Blake., MFB016; 3.5 x 5.5; Embossed with Blake's studio address. (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, seated male adult and a standing female adult with her arm around his shoulders, unidentified, circa 1926-1939, MFB017; 3.5 x 5.5 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, seated elderly male adult, identified as James W. White, circa 1918-1922, MFB018; 3.5 x 5.5; Stamped with Blake's studio address: "M. Blake Night and Day Photographer 384 W. Sumter Street, Charleston, S.C." (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, standing male adult, identified as Philips Michael Smalls, circa 1910-1918, MFB019; 3.5 x 5.5 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, male child standing on a chair, unidentified, circa 1926-1939. Photograph identified as by Blake., MFB020; 3.5 x 5.5; Embossed with Blake's studio address. (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, male adult, identified as E. H. Coit, undated, MFB021; 3.5 x 5.5 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, male child standing on a chair, unidentified, circa 1926-1939. Photograph identified as by Blake. Duplicate of photograph no. 20, MFB022; 3.5 x 5.5; Embossed with Blake's studio address. (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, seated male adult and a standing female adult with her arm around his shoulders, unidentified, circa 1926-1939. Photograph identified as by Blake, 384 W. Sumter Street, Charleston, S.C., MFB023; 3.5 x 5.5; Writing on Photograph: "Bennie and Wife." Embossed with Blake's studio address. (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, seated male adult, identified as Eddie Ford, 1932 June 10. Photograph identified as by Blake, 384 W. Sumter Street, Charleston, S.C., MFB024; 3.5 x 5.5; Writing on Photograph: "Eddie Ford. Taken June 10th 1932." Embossed with Blake's studio address. (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, standing female child holding a flower, unidentified, circa 1910-1918, MFB025; 3.5 x 5.5 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, standing female adult wearing a hat and a coat, identified as D. F. Murray, circa 1918-1922. Negative on file, MFB026; 3.5 x 5.5; Writing on Photograph: "D.F. Murray, Sumter St., Columbia SC." Stamped with Blake's studio address: "M. Blake Night and Day Photographer, 384 W. Sumter Street, Charleston, S.C." (Box 1)
  - Snapshot, two female adults sitting on the front porch of a house, unidentified, undated, MFB027; 3.5 x 2.75; Stamped "10011". (Box 1)
  - Snapshot, female adult standing and holding an infant at "#384", identified possibly as Mrs. Blake, undated, MFB028; 4.5 x 2.5 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, female adult, identified as Irene Green, circa 1926-1939. Same woman as in no. 4 but identified with a different name., MFB029; 3.5 x 5.5; Writing on Photograph: "Johns Island SC. Mrs. Irene Green." (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, standing female adult, unidentified, circa 1910-1918, MFB030; 3.5 x 5.5 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, seated child, identified as Leon Ignatius Ford, Jr., undated, MFB031; 3.5 x 5.5; Writing on Photograph: "Leon Ignatius Ford Jr. 1 yr 2 wks." (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, female adult standing outside on a path, unidentified, circa 1918-1922, MFB032; 3.5 x 5.5 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, standing female adult, unidentified, circa 1910-1918, MFB033; 3.5 x 5.5 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, seated female adult, identified as Helen Ford, circa 1918-1922, MFB034; 3.5 x 5.5; Writing on Photograph: "Mrs. Helen Ford." Stamped with Blake's studio address: " M. Blake Night and Day Photographer 384 W. Sumter Street, Charleston, S.C." (Box 1)
  - Snapshot, dog lying down, unidentified, undated, MFB035; 3 x 4.5 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, standing female adult, unidentified, circa 1918-1922, MFB036; 3.5 x 5.5 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, seated male adult, unidentified, circa 1910-1918, MFB037; 3.5 x 5.5; Stamped with Blake's studio address: " M.F. Blake View Photographer 12 W. Sumter Street. Phone 1341-L, Charleston, S.C." (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, female child and standing female adult with her arm around the shoulders of an older seated female adult, unidentified, circa 1926-1939. Photograph identified as by Blake, 384 W. Sumter Street, Charleston, S.C., MFB038; 3.5 x 5.5; Embossed with Blake's studio address. (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, seated male adult, identified as Eddie Ford, circa 1918-1922, MFB039; 3.5 x 5.5; Stamped with Blake's studio address: " M.F. Blake View Photographer 384 W. Sumter Street Charleston, S.C." (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, two standing female adults, unidentified, circa 1912-1915, MFB040; 3.5 x 5.5 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, female adult, unidentified, undated, MFB041; 1.375 x 1.75 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, two standing female young adults leaning on an older male child, unidentified, circa 1918-1922, MFB042; 3.5 x 5.5; Stamped with Blake's studio address: " M. Blake Night and Day Photographer 384 W. Sumter Street, Charleston, S.C." (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, standing female adult, unidentified, circa 1918-1922, MFB043; 3.5 x 5.5; Writing on Photograph: Stamped with Blake's studio address: " M. Blake Night and Day Photographer 384 W. Sumter Street, Charleston, S.C." (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, standing male child dressed in formal wear, unidentified, circa 1918-1922, MFB044; 3.5 x 5.5 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, seated child, unidentified, undated, MFB045; 3.25 x 5 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, male adult standing by a door, unidentified, circa 1918-1922, MFB046; 3.5 x 5.5; Stamped with Blake's studio address: " M.F. Blake 384 W. Sumter Street View Photographer Phone 1341-W, Charleston, S.C." (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, standing male child, unidentified, circa 1918-1922, MFB047; 3.5 x 5.5; Stamped with Blake's studio address: " M.F. Blake 384 W. Sumter Street View Photographer Phone 1341-W, Charleston, S.C." (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, seated infant, unidentified, undated, MFB048; 3.5 x 5.5 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, standing female adult, unidentified, circa 1910-1918, MFB049; 3.5 x 5.5 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, seated female adult, unidentified, circa 1918-1922. Photograph identified as by Blake, 384 W. Sumter Street, Charleston, S.C., MFB050; 3.5 x 5.5; Embossed with Blake's studio address. (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, infant posed on a bench, unidentified, circa 1926-1939. Photograph identified as by Blake, 384 W. Sumter Street, Charleston, S.C., MFB051; 3.5 x 5.5; Embossed with Blake's studio address. (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, seated male adult. Same photograph as no. 11., identified as Jesse E. Beard, a pastor of Morris Brown AME Church and vice president of the People's Federal Bank in Charleston, S.C., circa 1926-1939, MFB052; 3.5 x 5.5 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, standing female adult, identified as Jessie Rodrigues, circa 1918-1922, MFB053; 3.5 x 5.5; Stamped with Blake's studio address: " M. F. Blake Night and Day Photographer 384 W. Sumter Street, Charleston, S.C." (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, standing female adult, unidentified, circa 1910-1918, MFB054; 3.5 x 5.5 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, female adult, identified as Lucy Meyers, circa 1910-1918, MFB055; 3.5 x 5.5; Writing on Photograph: "Mrs. Lucy Meyers" (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, seated elderly male adult, identified as Sandy Simmons, circa 1926-1939, MFB056; 3.5 x 5.5; Embossed with Blake's studio address. (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, child standing on a chair and an infant seated on a chair, identified as Bennie children, circa 1926-1939. Same photograph as no. 16.Identified as by Blake., MFB057; 3.5 x 5.5, Writing on Photograph: "Bennie Children". Embossed with Blake's studio address. (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, seated male adult, identified as J. Donovan Moore, a music teacher, circa 1926-1939. Photograph identified as by Blake, 384 W. Sumter Street, Charleston, S.C., MFB058; 3.5 x 5.5; Embossed with Blake's studio address. (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, male adult, unidentified, circa 1926-1939, MFB059; 3.5 x 5.5 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, male adult, unidentified, circa 1918-1922, MFB060; 3.5 x 5.5 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, standing male adult in formal wear, unidentified, undated, MFB061; 3.25 x 5 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, male adult standing next to female adult who is wearing pants and holding a cigar, identified as Olivia Edith Garrett Wilson and Gustavius Sinkler Wilson, circa 1910-1922, MFB062; 3.5 x 5.5 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, male adult sitting on a chair outdoors, identified as M.A. Hollins, circa 1918-1922. Photograph identified as by Blake, 384 W. Sumter Street, Charleston, S.C., MFB063; 3.5 x 5.5; Embossed with Blake's studio address. (Box 1)
  - Snapshot, standing female adult and four younger females,identified as Allane Rodrigues, Henrietta Jones Rodrigues, Daisy Rodrigues, Dorothy, Hortense, undated, MFB064; 3.75 x 3; Embossed with Blake's studio address. (Box 1)
  - Snapshot, standing female adult and four younger females, identified as Allane Rodrigues, Henrietta Jones Rodrigues, Daisy Rodrigues, Dorothy, Hortense, undated. Same photograph as no. 64., MFB065; 3.75 x 3; Embossed with Blake's studio address. (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, male adult, unidentified, circa 1918-1922, MFB066; 3.5 x 5.5 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, five standing children, unidentified, circa 1910-1918. Negative on file., MFB067; 3.5 x 5.5; Stamped with Blake's studio address: " M.F. Blake View Photographer 12 W. Sumter Street. Phone 1341-L, Charleston, S.C." (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, standing female adult, unidentified, circa 1926-1939. Identified as by Blake, 384 W. Sumter., MFB068; 3.5 x 5.5; Embossed with Blake's studio address. (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, male adult, identified as John McQueen, circa 1926-1939, MFB069; 3.5 x 5.5; Writing on Photograph: "John McQueen" (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, male adult, identified as Jesse E. Beard, a pastor of Morris Brown AME Church and vice president of the People's Federal Bank in Charleston, S.C., circa 1926-1939. Same photograph as nos. 11 and 52. Identified as by Blake, 384 W. Sumter., MFB070; 3.5 x 5.5; Embossed with Blake's studio address. (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, female adult, identfied as Olivia Edith Garrett Wilson, circa 1926-1939. Photograph of another photograph. Identified as by Blake, 384 W. Sumter., MFB071; 3.5 x 5.5; Writing on Photograph: "Ollsey Gartett" (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, female adult, unidentified, circa 1918-1922, MFB072; 3.5 x 5.5 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, seated female adult, unidentified, circa 1918-1922, MFB073; 3.5 x 5.5 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, seated female adult, unidentified, circa 1910-1918, MFB074; 3.5 x 5.5 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, seated female adult using a telephone as a prop, unidentified, circa 1926-1939. Identified as by Blake, 384 W. Sumter. 2 negatives on file., MFB075; 3.5 x 5.5; Embossed with Blake's studio address. (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, 2 seated adult males playing checkers at a table outdoors and four adult males standing behind them, unidentified, circa 1913-1922. Negative on file., MFB076; 3.5 x 5.5 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, male adult, identified as Isiah Nathaniel Aiken, 1922 April 23, MFB077; 3.5 x 5.5; Writing on Photograph: "Sunday April 23 1922" (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, standing male adult, unidentified, circa 1910-1918, MFB078; 3.5 x 5.5 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, seated elderly female adult holding a small dog, standing child and two standing female adults, unidentified, circa 1910-1918. Photograph taken outdoors. Negative on file., MFB079; 3.5 x 5.5 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, seated female adult with two children, identified as Anna Beatrice Aiken, Isaiah Nathaniel Aiken, Jr., Arthur Aiken, circa 1918-1922, MFB080; 3.5 x 5.5 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, standing female adult, unidentified, circa 1910-1918. Same photograph as no. #30., MFB081; 3.5 x 5.5 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, seated female adult, unidentified, circa 1910-1918, MFB082; 3.5 x 5.5 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, two male adults, unidentified, circa 1918-1922. Identified as by Blake, 384 W. Sumter., MFB083; 3.5 x 5.5; Stamped with Blake's studio address: " M. F. Blake Night and Day Photographer 384 W. Sumter Street, Charleston, S.C." (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, standing female adult outdoors, unidentified, circa 1918-1922. Identified as by Blake, 384 W. Sumter., MFB084; 3.5 x 5.5 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, standing female adult and standing male adult, unidentified, circa 1910-1918, MFB085; 3.5 x 5.5 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, standing female young adult with her arm around seated young male adult, unidentified, circa 1926-1939. Identified as by Blake, 384 W. Sumter., MFB086; 3.5 x 5.5; Embossed with Blake's studio address. (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, female adult, unidentified, 20 February 1925. Identified as by Blake., MFB087; 3.5 x 5.5; Writing on Photograph: "Feb. 20th day 1925". Stamped with Blake's studio address: " M.F. Blake View Photographer 384 W. Sumter Street Charleston, S.C." (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, standing female child next to a doll seated on a chair, unidentified, circa 1918-1922. Identified as by Blake. Negative on file., MFB088; 3.5 x 5.5; Embossed with Blake's studio address. (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, seated male adult, unidentified, circa 1926-1939. Identified as by Blake, 384 W. Sumter., MFB089; 3.5 x 5.5; Embossed with Blake's studio address. (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, standing elderly male adult holding an open book, unidentified, circa 1918-1922. Identified as by Blake, 384 Sumter., MFB090; 3.5 x 5.5; Stamped with Blake's studio address: " M. F. Blake Night and Day Photographer 384 W. Sumter Street, Charleston, S.C." (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, standing elderly male adult holding a book, identified as Rev. Lowry Alston, circa 1918-1922. Identified as by Blake, 384 Sumter. Negative on file., MFB091; 3.5 x 5.5; Writing on Photograph: "Rev. Lowry Alston - #413 - Orange St. Georgetown S.C." Stamped with Blake's studio address: " M. F. Blake Night and Day Photographer 384 W. Sumter Street, Charleston, S.C.". (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, standing adult female and standing adult male on either side of a seated child in a chair, unidentified, circa 1918-1922, MFB092; 3.5 x 5.5 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, standing child, unidentified, circa 1910-1918, MFB093; 3.25 x 5.25 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, standing child, unidentified, circa 1910-1918, MFB094; 3.25 x 5.25 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, standing female adult holding a book, unidentified, circa 1926-1939. Identified as by Blake. Same photograph as no. 3., MFB095; 3.5 x 5.5; Embossed with Blake's studio address. (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, seated infant propped up on a chair, unidentified, 1933 June 19. Same photo as no. 13., MFB096; 3.5 x 5.5; Writing on Photograph: "June Thursday 1933 Pass (?) - 3 months old". Embossed with Blake's studio address. (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, adult male, identified as E. H. Coit, undated, MFB097; 3.25 x 4.25 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, adult male, identified as E. H. Coit, undated, MFB098; 3.25 x 4.25; Stamped with Blake's studio address: " M.F. Blake View Photographer 12 W. Sumter Street. Phone 1341-L, Charleston, S.C." (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, 2 seated adult females, identified as Evelyn Read, Agnes Read, circa 1926-1939.. Identified as by Blake., MFB099; 3.5 x 5.5; Embossed with Blake's studio address. (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, seated adult male, unidentified, undated, MFB100; 3.75 x 5.5 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, adult female, unidentified, circa 1918-1922. Identified as by Blake, 384 W. Sumter., MFB101; 3.5 x 5.5 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, adult female dressed in a man's suit, identified as Mary Buckingham Brown, circa 1926-1939. Negative on file., MFB102; 3.5 x 5.5 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, standing adult female, unidentified, circa 1918-1922. Identified as by Blake, 384 W. Sumter, MFB103; 3.5 x 5.5; Stamped with Blake's studio address: " M.F. Blake View Photographer 12 W. Sumter Street. Phone 1341-L, Charleston, S.C." (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, adult female, unidentified, circa 1918-1922. Identified as by Blake., MFB104; 3.5 x 5.5; Stamped with Blake's studio address: " M. F. Blake Night and Day Photographer 384 W. Sumter Street, Charleston, S.C." (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, seated adult female, identified as Pauline Buckingham, circa 1918-1922, MFB105; 3.5 x 5.5 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, elderly adult female, unidentified, circa 1918-1922, MFB106; 3.5 x 5.5 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, adult male, unidentified, circa 1926-1939. Identified as by Blake, 384 W. Sumter, MFB107; 3.5 x 5.5; Embossed with Blake's studio address. (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, standing male child next to an infant seated on a chair, unidentified, circa 1926-1939, MFB108; 3.5 x 5.5; Embossed with Blake's studio address. (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, standing adult female dressed in bridal wear, unidentified, circa 1926-1939. Identified as by Blake, 384 W. Sumter., MFB109; 3.5 x 5.5; Embossed with Blake's studio address. (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, adult male, unidentified, circa 1910-1918. Identified as by Blake., MFB110; 3.5 x 5.5 (Box 1)
  - Studio photograph, standing adult female, unidentified, undated. Mounted photograph identified as by William D. Clarke, a white photographer in Charleston, S.C., MFB111; 4.25 x 6.25 (Box 1)